YEN HUNG LIN

hello@yenhunglin.com yenhunglin.com

SKILLS

Experience in Visual, UIUX and Brand Design

App/Web Design
UI Library Mgmt.
UI Component design
Wireframing
App prototyping
Icon Design
Motion Design

Brand Design Print/Digital Design Packaging Design

Scripting Languages

HTML CSS Basic JS Basic Framer X

Computer Programs

Sketch Invision Zeplin -

Jira

After Effects

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign

Languages

Engish Mandarin Chinese Taiwanese

SELECTED RECOMMENDATIONS

Kai Haas // Director of UX at Engagio

Jeff is a true creative talent and powerful team player! He always delivers great results within short periods of time. Very efficient at design, he manages his time between all projects, tasks, and initiatives in the most professional of ways. He also strives to always find the perfect solution. Jeff is exactly who you want on your team!

Grant Grigorian //

Director of Product Management, Engagio

Jeff is an absolute pleasure to work with. We worked together closely on the product team and were able to iterate on many visual designs within a very short period of time: which led to more customer validation, more feature variations, more ideas, and a better product in the end. This rapid paced iteration and ideation would not be possible without Jeff on the team.

I highly recommend Jeff, and would love an opportunity to work with him in the future.

SELECTED EXPERIENCES

Engagio // San Mateo, CA 2018-Present, Visual, UI Designer

- Product Team: Work with PM, UX, and engineers to define the visual systems and the interactive elements of our app. Redefine and maintain UI library.
- Marketing Team: Collaborate on print, web, and motion designs. Define the brand system and translate the vibe of our brand into our products.

MOCACARE // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan 2017-2018, Visual, UI/UX Designer

- Product Team: Work on user research-based visual designs for MOCACARE app icons redesign and app pairing experience redesign.
- Marketing Team: Work on digital and print designs.
 Projects include MOACuff package, user manual redesign, 2017 and 2018 holiday web banner designs.

HTC // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan 2014-2015, Visual, Package Designer

- Participate in design process of HTC Vive and HTC 10 package design. Participate in 2015 visual design language conception with both packaging and industrial design team.
- Work with HTC innovation team on HTC 10 animation for internal presentation.
- Accompany designers to factories in Taiwan, meet with vendors to study new packaging materials, and build good work relationships with vendors.

San Francisco Art Institute // SF, CA 2014, Visual Design Intern

 Work with internal marketing team on weekly event poster designs, gallery show invitation designs, school publications, and school event photo documentation.

EDUCATION

California College of the Arts

2013, BFA in Graphic Design